keywordeye.co.uk 2015-02-14

# Privacy Policy | Keyword Eye

## Cookies and Privacy Policy

This policy explains how we, Keyword Eye Limited, use your personal information which you provide to us when using our website.

### What information do we collect about you?

We collect personal information from you when you order services from us or use our website. We also collect information when you complete any customer survey. We collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our websites.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the website.

The table below list the cookies we use. These cookies are seen as essential to the running of the website, without them, desktop, mobile and tablet devices will not display the images properly and the blog comments will not work.

Name | Set by/for | Description | Further reading  
---|---|---|---  
disqus_unique  
__qca  
__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz  
quantserve.com mc  
scorecardresearch.com UID  
scorecardresearch.com UIDR  
media.cdn.disqus.com testCookie | Disqus Comment system | We use a third party solution to handle our blog comments, this solution stores cookies to ease return use of the blog, further information can be found on their privacy policy. This is seen as an ESSENTIAL cookie and will always be stored in your web browser. | [The Disqus Privacy Policy](http://docs.disqus.com/help/30/ "Disqus Privacy Policy")  
  
The following table lists any cookies that are seen as non-essential to the workings of the website.

PLEASE NOTE, by switching off cookies, it will severely harm our business, we will no longer be able to track visits to our website, see what the most popular pages are or devices looking at our website, it will be the equivalent of running a sweet shop, blindfolded with no stock-taking facility available.

Name | Set by/for | Description | Further reading  
---|---|---|---  
__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz | Google Analytics | We use Google Analytics to allow us to analyse the traffic to our site and to review a number of statistics regarding our visitors. | [Click here for an overview of Google Analytics privacy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html "Google Privacy Policy")  
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). However, please note that if you choose to disable cookies, then parts of this website may not function correctly.

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### How will we use the information we collect from you?

Information that we collect from you is used to process your order and to manage your account. We may also use your information to email you about other products or services that we think may be of interest to you.

In processing your order we may send your information to credit reference and fraud prevention agencies.

### Access to your information

You have a right to request a copy of the information we hold on you at any time. Please email us if you would like to receive a copy of this information: [contact@keywordeye.com](mailto:contact@keywordeye.com). There will be a small charge for processing this request.

### Other Websites

Our website may have links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website. You should therefore read the privacy policies of the other websites when you are using those sites.
